suzannah.com 2009-02-23

# Privacy policy - Suzannah Dress Boutique

Please read our Privacy Policy carefully. This policy applies when you visit or surf our web site without purchasing any product, when you register with Suzannah.com / Dress-Boutique.com, and when you use our site for purchasing products. 

If you haven’t already done so, please also read our Terms and Conditions. 

Suzannah.com / Dress-Boutique.com values its customers and respects their privacy. We collect customer information in an effort to improve your shopping experience and to communicate with you about our products, services, contests and promotions. We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties. As described in this policy, we do, however, share your information with our affiliates and under certain circumstances, with third parties that provide services on our behalf or with whom we have partnered to offer a particular product or service. 

This policy describes the personal information we collect about you, why we collect it, how we use it and when we share it with third parties. Our policy also describes the choices you can make about how we collect and use your information. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, you can always contact Suzannah.com / Dress-Boutique.com customer service. Email: 

If our information practices change in the future, we will post an updated policy on our website. You can tell if the policy has changed by checking the revision date that appears at the end of this policy. You may exercise your choices about how we collect and use your information at any time. 

#### **Our Privacy Policy **

What kind of information does Suzannah.com / Dress-Boutique.com collect?   
When you visit, register or order products or services you may be asked to provide certain information about yourself including your name, contact details and credit or debit card information. 

We may also collect information about your usage of our website as well as information about you from messages you post to the website and e-mails or letters you send to us. 

To maintain customer service standards and to assist staff training, we may record and monitor incoming calls. 

How does Suzannah.com / Dress-Boutique.com use my information?  
The information you provide to us may be accessed by or given to third parties some of whom may be located outside the European Economic Area who act for us for the purposes set out in this policy or for other purposes approved by you. Those parties process information, fulfill and deliver orders, process credit card payments and provide support services on our behalf. We may also pass aggregate information on the usage of our website to third parties but this will not include information that can be used to identify you. 

Finally, if our business enters into a joint venture with or is sold to or merged with another business entity, your information may be disclosed to our new business partners or owners. 

Countries outside the European Economic Area do not always have strong data protection laws. However, we will always take steps to ensure that your information is used by third parties in accordance with this policy. 

Unless required to do so by law, we will not otherwise share, sell or distribute any of the information you provide to us without your consent. 

Does Suzannah.com / Dress-Boutique.com share my information with third parties?  
We contract with service providers to maintain and manage our customer information, to fulfill promotions and to communicate with our customers. We do not authorize any of these service providers to make any other use of your information. 

In addition, when we team up with another company to offer or provide products, services, contests or promotions, we may compare our customer list with theirs to identify our common customers. Both Suzannah.com and our marketing partners may use that information to fulfill our respective obligations to you and for future promotional activities. 

When we offer contests and promotions, with or without a marketing partner, you may be required to provide certain personal information in order to participate. In these cases, we will give you the choice not to receive e-mail messages or other communications from us regarding our products, services, contests, and promotions when you register for the above. In this case, however, we may still need to contact you, for example, to notify winners and to fulfill promotional obligations. 

In the unlikely event of a sale of some or all of our business, Suzannah.com / Dress-Boutique.com Ltd will disclose your personal information to a purchaser that agrees to abide by the terms and conditions of this privacy policy. 

Suzannah.com / Dress-Boutique.com Ltd reserves the right to disclose information about you as required by law, in response to legal process and law enforcement requests, and as necessary to protect the property, interests and rights of Suzannah.com / Dress-Boutique.com Ltd, its affiliates, and others. 

How do I exercise my choices about receiving promotional communications?  
We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive promotional information from us or our affiliated brands, or if you do not want us to use your information to enhance your shopping experience, please let us know by email 

.  Please be sure to include your full name and the e-mail address you used when you registered with or made a purchase from us. If you ask us to remove your name and address from promotional lists, we will maintain your name in a “do not contact” file to ensure that we can honor your request. It may take up to 10 days to process your e-mail request, and 6-8 weeks to process your postal mail request, during which period you may continue to receive communications from Suzannah.com / Dress-Boutique.com Ltd. 

Please also note that when you purchase from us, we will continue to confirm your order by e-mail. In addition, we may also need to contact you via phone, e-mail or postal mail with other questions regarding your order. 

What are cookies? How does Suzannah.com / Dress-Boutique.com use cookies on its site?  
A cookie is a small data file that websites often store on your computers hard drive when you visit their sites. A cookie may contain information, such as a unique user ID that websites use to track the pages of the sites you’ve visited. We use cookies but do not store personally identifiable information in your cookie. 

We use cookies in order to improve your shopping experience. Cookies enable us to keep track of your order as you shop on our site. 

Through our use of cookies, we also track and maintain the identity of the website you visited immediately prior to visiting our website. We do not otherwise track any information about your use of other websites. 

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you turn off cookies, though, we will not be able to track your order to enable you to purchase from our site. Nor will we be able to recognize you as a registered user, which allows you to access your account information. 

Is my information secure?  
Protecting your credit card and order information is important to us. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect your online order information as it is transmitted over the Internet.  
SSL is the gold standard in Internet encryption technology, which means it is a highly sophisticated method of scrambling data as it travels from your computer to our websites servers. 

Some versions of browsers and some firewalls do not permit communication through secure servers like the ones we use to process orders at Suzannah.com / Dress-Boutique.com. To check the security of your connection, look at the lower left-hand corner of your browser window after accessing the server. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending on your browser), then SSL is active. You can also double-check by looking at the URL line of your browser. When accessing a secure server, the first characters of the site address will change from “http” to “https.” 

If your browser or firewall does not support SSL, you will not be able to connect to the server, which means you wont be able to mistakenly place an order through an unsecured connection. 

Effective 1st August, 2008 

This website uses etracker technology ([www.etracker.com](http://www.etracker.com/)) to collect visitor behaviour data. This data is collected anonymously to be used for marketing and optimisation purposes. All visitor data is saved using an anonymous user ID to aggregate a usage profile. Cookies may be used to collect and save this data, but the data remains strictly anonymous. The data will not be used to identify a visitor personally and are not aggregated with any personal data. The collection and storage of data may be [refused](http://www.etracker.com/privacy?et=\[YOUR%20SECURITY%20CODE\]) at any time with respect to subsequent services.
